Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List:
  - Griffin, Ernest Otto, Jr. (Box 21)
  - Griffith, John (Box 21)
  - Griggs, Lillian Baker (Box 21)
  - Grimson, Keith Sanford, (2 Folders) (Box 21)
  - Grislis, Egil (Box 21)
  - Grosch, Kay Lichy (Box 22)
  - Grosch, William N. (Box 22)
  - Gross, Paul M., (8 Folders) (Box 22)
  - Gross, Steven J. (Box 23)
  - Grout, Julia Rebecca (Box 23)
  - Grubb, Barbara (Box 23)
  - Grzybowski, Kazimierz (Box 23)
  - Gudger, William D. (Box 23)
  - Gulick, Floyd (Box 23)
  - Guthrie, William Keith Chapman (Box 23)
  - Gutknetcht, John W. (Box 23)
  - Guttman, Norman (Box 23)
  - Guy, Albert G. (Box 23)
  - Haas, William Elmer (Box 23)
  - Haines, Howard N. (Box 23)
  - Halderman, John W. (Box 23)
  - Halfond, Murray Michael (Box 23)
  - Hall, Dwight H. (Box 23)
  - Hall, Frank G. (Box 23)
  - Hall, Louise (Box 23)
  - Hall, Stanford R. (Box 23)
  - Hall, Thor (Box 23)
  - Hall, William Holland (Box 23)
  - Hallowell, John H. (Box 23)
  - Hamblen, Edwin Crowell (Box 23)
  - Hamill, R. Wilkins III (Box 23)
  - Hamilton, Earl Jefferson (Box 23)
  - Hamilton, Iain, (4 Folders) (Box 23)
  - Hamilton, William Baskerville, Jr. (Box 23)
  - Hamlin, William Thomas (Box 24)
  - Hammond, W. Michael (Box 24)
  - Hampikian, Aram (Box 24)
  - Handler, Phillip, (3 Folders) (Box 24)
  - Hanes, Frederic M. (Box 24)
  - Hanna, Frank Alonzo (Box 24)
  - Hansen, John P. (Box 24)
  - Hansen-Pruss, Oscar Carl Edward (Box 24)
  - Hanson, Earl T. (Box 24)
  - Hardorp, Detlef (Box 24)
  - Hargitt, George Thomas (Box 24)
  - Harp, Tom (Box 24)
  - Harrar, Elwood S. (Box 24)
  - Harrawood, Paul (Box 24)
  - Harriman, Philip D. (Box 24)
  - Harris, Jerome (Box 24)
  - Harris, T. Reginald (Box 24)
  - Harrison, Evelyn J. (Box 24)
  - Harrison, Francis P. (Box 24)
  - Hart, Hornell, (2 Folders) (Box 24)
  - Hart, Hornell (Box 25)
  - Hart, Julian D., (4 Folders) (Box 25)
  - Hart, Leonard M. (Box 25)
  - Hartley, Herman O. (Box 25)
  - Hartwig, Gerald W. (Box 25)
  - Harward, Stephen C. (Box 25)
  - Harwell, George Corbin (Box 25)
  - Hasbrouck, Francis M. (Box 25)
  - Haslam, Charles Linn (Box 25)
  - Hatley, Charles Cleveland (Box 25)
  - Hauser, Charles Roy (Box 25)
  - Hawes, Catherine (Box 25)
  - Hawley, Willis (Box 25)
  - Haywood, Charles Lewis, Jr. (Box 25)
  - Haywood, Ernest Lee (Box 25)
  - Hebb, Malcolm Hayden (Box 25)
  - Heckscher, William S. (Box 25)
  - Hedges, Inez (Box 25)
  - Hedstrom, Donald (Box 25)
  - Helling, Martin (Box 25)
  - Hemlick, Caroline (Box 25)
  - Henderson-James, Douglas (Box 25)
  - Hendrix, James Max (Box 25)
  - Hendrix, James Paisley (Box 25)
  - Hendrix, Johnny (Box 25)
  - Hendrix, Mildred L. (Box 26)
  - Heninger, Simeon Kahn, Jr. (Box 26)
  - Henricksen, G.C. (Box 26)
  - Henry, Stuart C. (Box 26)
  - Henson, Charles Ward, III (Box 26)
  - Herlinger, Jan William (Box 26)
  - Herpok, Franz J. (Box 26)
  - Herr, David Guy (Box 26)
  - Herring, Herbert James, (2 Folders) (Box 26)
  - Hesser, Frederick Harrison (Box 26)
  - Hetherington, Duncan C. (Box 26)
  - Heyman, Albert (Box 26)
  - Hickman, Franklin Simpson (Box 26)
  - Hickman, John Bamber (Box 26)
  - Hicks, Spears (Box 26)
  - Hickson, Arthur O. (Box 26)
  - High, Sherrill (Box 26)
  - Hight, Timothy Kenyon (Box 26)
  - Hill, Dan W. (Box 26)
  - Hill, David W. (Box 26)
  - Hill, Douglas (Box 26)
  - Hill, G. Watts, Sr. (Box 26)
  - Hillerbrand, Hans J. (Box 26)
  - Hillman, Edgar L. (Box 26)
  - Hirschman, Charles (Box 26)
  - Hoadley, John F. (Box 26)
  - Hobbs, Marcus Edwin, (2 Folders) (Box 27)
  - Hobbs, William H. (Box 27)
  - Hodges, Luther, Jr. (Box 27)
  - Hodges, Ronald (Box 27)
  - Hoffer, Jerry (Box 27)
  - Hohman, Leslie (Box 27)
  - Holland, Clyde Nelson (Box 27)
  - Holler, Walker W. (Box 27)
  - Hollinshead, William H. (Box 27)
  - Hollister, William F. (Box 27)
  - Hollyday, Frederic (Box 27)
  - Holton, Frances V. (Box 27)
  - Holton, Holland (Box 27)
  - Hon, Ralph C. (Box 27)
  - Hoover, Calvin Bryce, (4 Folders) (Box 27)
  - Hopkins, Dwight L. (Box 27)
  - Hopkins, Everett, (2 Folders) (Box 27)
  - Horack, Hugo Claude (Box 28)
  - Horn, Edward C. (Box 28)
  - Horowicz, Paul (Box 28)
  - Horton, Charles (Box 28)
  - Horton, Melinda (Box 28)
  - Hoskin, Robert E. (Box 28)
  - Houpt, Jeffrey (Box 28)
  - House, James S. (Box 28)
  - Howard, Emma J. (Box 28)
  - Howard, J.W. (Box 28)
  - Howard, W. Kenneth (Box 28)
  - Howe, Harold, II (Box 28)
  - Hubbell, Jay B. (Box 28)
  - Huber, Max (Box 28)
  - Huber, Thomas (Box 28)
  - Huestis, Charles B. (Box 28)
  - Hughes, George M. (Box 28)
  - Hughes, John S. (Box 28)
  - Hughes-Schrader, Sally (Box 28)
  - Huling, Porter B. (Box 28)
  - Hull, Robert (Box 28)
  - Hull, Wayland (Box 28)
  - Hull, William N.H. (Box 28)
  - Humm, Harold J. (Box 28)
  - Humphrey, Betty M. (Box 28)
  - Humphrey, Don Dougan (Box 28)
  - Hunt, Samuel R. (Box 28)
  - Hunter, Wanda S. (Box 28)
  - Hurd, David (Box 28)
  - Hurlburt, Allan S. (Box 28)
  - Hutcheson, Ann (Box 28)
  - Hyatt, Robert P. (Box 28)
  - Ilkow, Peter (Box 28)
  - Ingles, Thelma (Box 28)
  - Ingram, James M. (Box 28)
  - Ingram, O. Kelly (Box 28)
  - Innis, John Woodson (Box 28)
  - Irving, William Henry (Box 28)
  - Isenberg, Sheldon (Box 28)
  - Isley, Joseph K. (Box 28)
  - Jackson, David K. (Box 29)
  - Jackson, John N. (Box 29)
  - Jackson, (Mrs.) J.N. (Box 29)
  - Jackson, Richard L. (Box 29)
  - Jackson, Robert J.V (Box 29)
  - Jacobansky, Ann. (Box 29)
  - Jacobs, Miriam J. (Box 29)
  - Jaeger, Boi Jon (Box 29)
  - James, Carl Clifton (Box 29)
  - Janocraft, A. (Box 29)
  - Jantz, Harold (Box 29)
  - Jarboe, Wallace E. (Box 29)
  - Jarrard, Norman E. (Box 29)
  - Jefferies, Dwight (Box 29)
  - Jeffers, Frances C. (Box 29)
  - Jeffers, Katharine R. (Box 29)
  - Jeffs, Peter W. (Box 29)
  - Jelovsek, Frederick (Box 29)
  - Jenkins, Marianna (Box 29)
  - Jenkins, Robert M. (Box 29)
  - Jenks, Alan W. (Box 29)
  - Jennings, Ralph E. (Box 29)
  - Jensen, Howard E. (Box 29)
  - Jensen, Wallace W. (Box 29)
  - Jewell, Malcolm E. (Box 29)
  - Jewett, Paul H. (Box 29)
  - Jiminez, John P. (Box 29)
  - Jobe, James K. (Box 29)
  - Joerg, Frederick Charles (Box 29)
  - Johnsen, Thomas N., Jr. (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Charles E. (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Charles E., Jr. (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Cranford (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Frank L. (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Franklin P. (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Gordon Lee (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Lawrence E. (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Terry W. (Box 29)
  - Johnsrude, Irwin S. (Box 29)
  - Johnston, Christopher (Box 29)
  - Johnston, John Devereaux, Jr. (Box 29)
  - Johnston, Lemuel Roy (Box 29)
  - Jones, Claudius Parks (Box 29)
  - Jones, Hunter (Box 29)
  - Jones, Oliver W. (Box 29)
  - Jones, Robert R., Jr. (Box 29)
  - Jones, (Sara) Elizabeth (Box 29)
  - Jones, Thomas T. (Box 29)
  - Jordan, Archibald Currie (Box 29)
  - Jordan, Brady Rimbey (Box 29)
  - Jordan, Charles E., (2 Folders) (Box 29)
  - Jordan, Lemuel R. (Box 30)
  - Joyner, George W. (Box 30)
  - Judd, Mary (Box 30)
  - Kaiser, Helen (Box 30)
  - Kalat, James (Box 30)
  - Kale, William A. (Box 30)
  - Kamin, Henry (Box 30)
  - Kammerer, Charlene (Box 30)
  - Kane, William J. (Box 30)
  - Kantner, George (Box 30)
  - Kao, Tien-Cheng (Box 30)
  - Kapoor, Shankar Nath (Box 30)
  - Karwan, Kirk (Box 30)
  - Kattan, Nicholas (Box 30)
  - Kaufman, Nathan (Box 30)
  - Kaufman, Wallace V. (Box 30)
  - Keane, William M. (Box 30)
  - Kearns, Nancy Jean (Box 30)
  - Kearns, Ned S. (Box 30)
  - Kearney, Robert N. (Box 30)
  - Keech, James M. (Box 30)
  - Keese, Peter G. (Box 30)
  - Keever, Catherine (Box 30)
  - Keller, Catherine (Box 30)
  - Kelley, James M, Jr. (Box 30)
  - Kelley, William H. (Box 30)
  - Kelley, William N. (Box 30)
  - Kelvin, Frederick Maxwell (Box 30)
  - Kemp, Edward H. (Box 30)
  - Kempner, Walter (Box 30)
  - Keniston, Hayward (Box 30)
  - Kennedy, Fronde (Box 30)
  - Kennedy, James S. (Box 30)
  - Kenney, Philip E. (Box 30)
  - Kenyon, Van L., Jr. (Box 30)
  - Keppel-Jones, Arthur Mervyn (Box 30)
  - Kerby, Grace P. (Box 30)
  - Ketterer, Stephen (Box 30)
  - Khoury, Maroon B. (Box 30)
  - Kiernan, Eileen Dorothy (Box 30)
  - Kilburn, Kaye Hatch (Box 30)
  - Kilgo, John C. (Box 30)
  - Kilpatrick, Wylie (Box 30)
  - Kimble, Gregory Adams (Box 30)
  - King, Charles Herschel (Box 30)
  - King, John B. (Box 30)
  - Kinkead, Duncan T. (Box 30)
  - Kinney, Thomas (Box 30)
  - Kinross-Wright, Vernon (Box 30)
  - Kipnis, David M. (Box 30)
  - Kirk, Ralph Gary (Box 30)
  - Kirkendale, Warren (Box 30)
  - Kirkwood, Marion R. (Box 30)
  - Kistler, Phil (Box 30)
  - Kiwanuka, Matia S.M. (Box 30)
  - Klabes, Gunter (Box 30)
  - Klause, Joseph Edward (Box 30)
  - Klavins, Janis (Box 30)
  - Klein, James Raymond (Box 30)
  - Klein, Robert F. (Box 30)
  - Klein, Theodore George (Box 30)
  - Klenz, William (Box 30)
  - Kline, John (Box 30)
  - Klopfer, Walter George (Box 30)
  - Knight, Douglas M., (9 Folders) (Box 31)
  - Knight, Douglas M., (2 Folders) (Box 32)
  - Knight, Robert, Jr. (Box 32)
  - Knight, W.D. (Box 32)
  - Knisley, William Hagerman (Box 32)
  - Knox, Edward M., Jr. (Box 32)
  - Knox, (Mrs.) Ellen Matteson (Box 32)
  - Knox, Paul R. (Box 32)
  - Koch, Ruth M. (Box 32)
  - Koch, Sigmund (Box 32)
  - Koenig, J. Frank (Box 32)
  - Koesy, Sheldon Fred (Box 32)
  - Kohler, Ivo (Box 32)
  - Kohn, Henry I. (Box 32)
  - Koontz, Harold D. (Box 32)
  - Korkes, Seymour (Box 32)
  - Korstian, Clarence F. (Box 32)
  - Kosting, Peter R. (Box 32)
  - Kostyo, Jack L. (Box 32)
  - Koury, George (Box 32)
  - Kramer, Paul J., (2 Folders) (Box 32)
  - Kramer, Robert (Box 32)
  - Krause, David R. (Box 32)
  - Kraybill, Edward K. (Box 32)
  - Kraycirik, E.T. (Box 32)
  - Kreps, Clifton (Box 32)
  - Kreps, Juanita, (2 Folders) (Box 32)
  - Kreps, Juanita, (2 Folders) (Box 33)
  - Kritzler, Henry (Box 33)
  - Krumel, Charles Albert (Box 33)
  - Krynski, Magnus J. (Box 33)
  - Kubiszewski, Robert Joseph (Box 33)
  - Kuc, Susan (Box 33)
  - Kuder, G. Frederic (Box 33)
  - Kulski, Wladyslaw W. (Box 33)
  - Kunkle, E. Charles (Box 33)
  - Kunstmann, John G. (Box 33)
  - Kurtz, Stanley M. (Box 33)
  - La Barre, Maurine (Box 33)
  - La Barre, Weston (Box 33)
  - Lacy, Creighton (Box 33)
  - Landers, Maurice (Box 33)
  - Landon, Charles (Box 33)
  - Lane, James (Box 33)
  - Langford, Thomas A. (Box 33)
  - Langley, John H. (Box 33)
  - Lanning, John Tate (Box 33)
  - Laprade, William T. (Box 34)
  - Larson, Arthur, (6 Folders) (Box 34)
  - Larson, Arthur (Box 35)
  - Lassaw, Ibram (Box 35)
  - Laszlo, John (Box 35)
  - Latty, Elvin (Box 35)
  - Lauf, Peter K. (Box 35)
  - Lavacca, Mariann DiMinno (Box 35)
  - Lazarus, Gerald Sylvan (Box 35)
  - Leach, Richard H. (Box 35)
  - Leary, Lewis (Box 35)
  - Leavitt, Sturgis E. (Box 35)
  - Lebovitz, Harold E. (Box 35)
  - Lecocq, Frank Robert (Box 35)
  - Lee, F. Graham (Box 35)
  - Lee, Howard (Box 35)
  - Lefler, B. Wesley (Box 35)
  - Leftwich, George E., Jr. (Box 35)
  - Lehane, Stephen F. (Box 35)
  - Leighton, Clare (Box 35)
  - Leist, George (Box 35)
  - LeMay, John C. (Box 35)
  - Lemert, Benjamin Franklin (Box 35)
  - Lemkin, Raphael (Box 35)
  - Leonard, Henry Siggins (Box 35)
  - Leshin, Richard (Box 35)
  - Leslie, John B. (Box 35)
  - Lester, Richard A. (Box 35)
  - Lester, Richard G. (Box 35)
  - Le Tourneau, Joseph R. (Box 35)
  - Levin, Betsy (Box 36)
  - Levy, Harry L. (Box 36)
  - Levy, Nelson L. (Box 36)
  - Lewicki, Roy I. (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Harold Gregg (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Harold W. (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Hubert Murry (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Leroy (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Martha Modena (Box 36)
  - Lewis, Ralph Elton (Box 36)
  - Leyte-Vidal, Jesus (Box 36)
  - Liacouras, Peter James (Box 36)
  - Lichtenstein, Sara (Box 36)
  - Lievsay, John Leon (Box 36)
  - Lih, Lars (Box 36)
  - Linebarger, Paul M. A. (Box 36)
  - Linderoth, L. Sigred, Jr. (Box 36)
  - Linke, William Richard (Box 36)
  - Linton, Thomas L. (Box 36)
  - Livingood, Charles H., Jr. (Box 36)
  - Llerena, Mario (Box 36)
  - Llewellyn, Charles E., Jr. (Box 36)
  - Lockey, Donald V. (Box 36)
  - London, Edith (Box 36)
  - London, Frits (Box 36)
  - Long, Charles H. (Box 36)
  - Long, Croft (Box 36)
  - Long, Sam (Box 36)
  - Longley, William (Box 36)
  - Loosen, Peter C. (Box 36)
  - Loro, Albert D., Jr. (Box 36)
  - Lowenbach, Hans (Box 36)
  - Lowndes, Charles L. B. (Box 36)
  - Luger, Michael L. (Box 36)
  - Lumiansky, Robert M. (Box 36)
  - Lundeberg, Olav K. (Box 36)
  - Lundholm, Helge (Box 36)
  - Luther, J. Scott (Box 37)
  - Lyman, Richard S. (Box 37)
  - Lynn, William S., Jr. (Box 37)
  - Mabry, William A. (Box 37)
  - MacConochie, Ian O. (Box 37)
  - Macduff, John N. (Box 37)
  - MacMillan, Louis R. (Box 37)
  - Mace, Arthur E., Jr. (Box 37)
  - Mace, Jennie A. (Box 37)
  - Mack, George (Box 37)
  - Mackler, Hyman (Box 37)
  - Magalhaes, Hulda (Box 37)
  - Maggs, Douglas B. (Box 37)
  - Maguire, Robert (Box 37)
  - Mahnensmith, Rex L. (Box 37)
  - Mahoney, Bary S. (Box 37)
  - Maier, Charles (Box 37)
  - Maker, Philip T. (Box 37)
  - Majesky, John E. (Box 37)
  - Malinasky, Frank N. (Box 37)
  - Malone, Eva (Box 37)
  - Malone, Thomas P. (Box 37)
  - Manchester, Alan Krebs (Box 37)
  - Mandell, Richard Donald (Box 37)
  - Manikam, Rajah B. (Box 37)
  - Manly, Jethro O. (Box 37)
  - Mann, Charles E. (Box 37)
  - Mann, Everett James (Box 37)
  - Mann, Glenn E. (Ted) (Box 37)
  - Manry, James C. (Box 37)
  - Manschreck, Clyde L. (Box 37)
  - Mansergh, Nicholas (Box 37)
  - Marberry, J.O. (Box 37)
  - Margolis, George (Box 37)
  - Mark, Alan Francis (Box 37)
  - Markee, Joseph E. (Box 37)
  - Markham, Charles Blackwell (Box 37)
  - Markman, Sydney (Box 37)
  - Marney, Carlyle (Box 37)
  - Marsh, Robert Mortimer (Box 37)
  - Marshall, Peter (Box 37)
  - Marshall, Roger (Box 37)
  - Marshall, William H. (Box 37)
  - Martin, Donald Stover (Box 37)
  - Massengill, Raymond (Box 37)
  - Massey, Marilyn Chapin (Box 37)
  - Mattingly, Capitola (Box 37)
  - Matthews, Minetta (Box 37)
  - Maughan, William (Box 37)
  - Maxson, Wayne S. (Box 37)
  - Maxwell, William Cary (Box 37)
  - Mayesky, Mary E. (Box 37)
  - Mayo, Henry Bertram (Box 37)
  - McBryde, Angus Murdoch (Box 38)
  - McBryde, Gerald W. (Box 38)
  - McCall, Adeline (Box 38)
  - McCarty, Gale A. (Box 38)
  - McClain, Joseph A., Jr. (Box 38)
  - McCloy, Shelby Thomas (Box 38)
  - McClure, Wallace (Box 38)
  - McDermott, Malcolm (Box 38)
  - McDonald, Alexander Donald (Box 38)
  - McDougall, William (Box 38)
  - McFeaters, C.P. (Box 38)
  - McGough, William E. (Box 38)
  - McGrath, Daniel (Box 38)
  - McGrath, Diane (Box 38)
  - McHugh, Gelolo, (2 Folders) (Box 38)
  - McIlrath, Leo (Box 38)
  - McIntosh, Henry (Box 38)
  - McKay, Martha (Box 38)
  - McKinney, John Clifford (Box 38)
  - McLarty, Furman Gordon (Box 38)
  - McLean, Edward (Box 38)
  - McLelland, Robert (Box 38)
  - McLeod, Robert Melvin (Box 38)
  - McManus, Mary I. (Box 38)
  - McMurray, Thomas J. (Box 38)
  - Meade, Mary E. (Box 39)
  - Meier, Otto, Jr. (Box 39)
  - Meiller, Joan (Box 39)
  - Meira, Joao Alves (Box 39)
  - Melges, Frederick Towne (Box 39)
  - Melion, Walter S. (Box 39)
  - Mendell, Lorne (Box 39)
  - Menefee, E.E. "Lige" (Box 39)
  - Mengel, Charles E. (Box 39)
  - Menkin, Valy (Box 39)
  - Mennini, Louis (Box 39)
  - Menzel, Daniel B. (Box 39)
  - Menzies, Robert J. (Box 39)
  - Meriam, James Lathrop (Box 39)
  - Mericle, Mary Fontaine (Box 39)
  - Metcalf, Zeno Payne (Box 39)
  - Meyers, Edward (Box 39)
  - Meyvaert, Paul (Box 39)
  - Michalak, Victor (Box 39)
  - Michlin, Michael (Box 39)
  - Miksis, Michael John (Box 39)
  - Milam, D.F. (Box 39)
  - Milbrath, Lester (Box 39)
  - Mildram, Robert C. (Box 39)
  - Miles, Edward Roy Cecil (Box 39)
  - Mill, W. Robert (Box 39)
  - Miller, Christine (Box 39)
  - Miller, Donald T. (Box 39)
  - Miller, Henry K., Jr. (Box 39)
  - Miller, John Noel (Box 39)
  - Miller, Joseph (Box 39)
  - Miller, Justin (Box 39)
  - Miller, Lowell Stephen (Box 39)
  - Miller, Martin (Box 39)
  - Miller, Maude McCracken (Box 39)
  - Miller, Robert W. (Box 39)
  - Miller, William James (Box 39)
  - Mimms, Christine (Box 39)
  - Mims, Edwin (Box 39)
  - Minah, Theodore H. (Box 39)
  - Mitcham, C.L. (Box 39)
  - Mitchell, Fannie Y. (Box 39)
  - Mitchell, Frank Kirby (Box 39)
  - Mitchell, Jo Anne (Box 39)
  - Mobley, Mark A. (Box 39)
  - Moize, Vivian (Box 39)
  - Molina, Alexander W. (Box 39)
  - Moltman, D. Jurgen (Box 39)
  - Monroe, Gary S. (Box 39)
  - Monsman, Gerald (Box 39)
  - Moon, Bruce E. (Box 39)
  - Moore, Ann Lee S. (Box 39)
  - Moore, James (Box 39)
  - Morey, Richard C. (Box 39)
  - Morgan, Carlisle Lee, Jr. (Box 39)
  - Morrow, Sue Ann (Box 39)
  - Moser, Louise (Box 39)
  - Mueller, Earl George (Box 39)
  - Mueller, Julia (Box 39)
  - Muller, Yvonne (Box 39)
  - Mulligan, Thomas (Box 39)
  - Murphy, Roland E. (Box 39)
  - Murray, Michael (Box 39)
  - Murray, William D. (Box 39)
  - Musante, Gerard (Box 40)
  - Myers, Hiram E. (Box 40)
  - Myers, Jack Duane, Jr. (Box 40)
  - Myers, William A. (Box 40)
  - Nagami, Keio (Box 40)
  - Nagaya, Hiroshi (Box 40)
  - Nagey, David A. (Box 40)
  - Nagin, Daniel (Box 40)
  - Narahasi, Toshio (Box 40)
  - Nash, James L. (Box 40)
  - Naumann, Dorothy Ethel (Box 40)
  - Nawaz, Mahomed K. (Box 40)
  - Neale, William McCormick (Box 40)
  - Neece, George (Box 40)
  - Neff, James A. (Box 40)
  - Negley, Glenn (Box 40)
  - Neilson, Robert H. (Box 40)
  - Nelson, Charles E. (Box 40)
  - Nelson, Ernest William (Box 40)
  - Nelson, Norman Kent (Box 40)
  - Nelson, Roland H. (Box 40)
  - Nesbitt, Marion Wilson (Box 40)
  - Neurath, Hans (Box 40)
  - Neville, Charles W. (Box 40)
  - Newman, Gustave (Box 40)
  - Newsome, Clarence (Box 40)
  - Newson, Henry Winston (Box 40)
  - Nichols, Claude R. (Box 40)
  - Nicholson, William McNeal (Box 40)
  - Nielson, Harry Stewart (Box 40)
  - Nielsen, Walter Mckinley (Box 40)
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous, (2 Folders) (Box 40)
  - Normon, John G. (Box 40)
  - Nordheim, Lother Wolfgang (Box 40)
  - North, Jeremy (Box 40)
  - North, William Charles (Box 40)
  - Obrist, Walter D. (Box 40)
  - Ocker, John M. (Box 41)
  - Oddson, Terrence Andrew (Box 41)
  - Odum, Guy L. (Box 41)
  - O'Fallon, William Michael (Box 41)
  - Olanow, C. Warren (Box 41)
  - Olive, David Leon (Box 41)
  - Oosting, Henry John (Box 41)
  - Orgain, Edward S. (Box 41)
  - Orleans, Tracy (Box 41)
  - Ormandy, Roderick B. (Box 41)
  - Ormond, Jesse M. (Box 41)
  - O'Rourke, Mark (Box 41)
  - Osofsky, Stephen Gary (Box 41)
  - Osterman, Marie (Box 41)
  - Ostrom, Dewey A. (Box 41)
  - Outler, Albert C. (Box 41)
  - Overman, John R. (Box 41)
  - Owen, Bruce M. (Box 41)
  - Owens, William G. (Box 41)
  - Pagan, Francisco Mariano (Box 41)
  - Painter, Joyce (Box 41)
  - Palmer, Aubrey E. (Box 41)
  - Palmore, Erdman, (2 Folders) (Box 41)
  - Parham, William E. (Box 41)
  - Parker, Andrew D. (Box 41)
  - Parker, Harold T. (Box 41)
  - Parker, Joseph B. (Box 41)
  - Parker, Scott (Box 41)
  - Parks, Richard (Box 41)
  - Parrent, Allan M. (Box 41)
  - Parsons, Oscar A. (Box 41)
  - Paschal, Joel Francis (Box 41)
  - Patrick, Ransom Rathbone (Box 41)
  - Patterson, F.M. Simmons (Box 41)
  - Patterson, Karl B. (Box 41)
  - Patterson, Robert Leet (Box 41)
  - Patton, Frances Gray (Box 41)
  - Patton, Lewis (Box 41)
  - Patton, William R. (Box 41)
  - Pearce, Richard (Box 42)
  - Pearse, A.S. (Box 42)
  - Pearson, Birger A. (Box 42)
  - Peavy, Marion (Box 42)
  - Peck, Richard (Box 42)
  - Peele, Talmage L. (Box 42)
  - Pemberton, Mary Norcott (Box 42)
  - Penrod, Kenneth E. (Box 42)
  - Pensak, Lewis (Box 42)
  - Pepper, Joseph and Barbara (Box 42)
  - Peppler, Charles William (Box 42)
  - Perivier, Jacques-Henri (Box 42)
  - Perlmutt, Louis M. (Box 42)
  - Perlzweig, William A. (Box 42)
  - Perry, Edmund Franklin (Box 42)
  - Perry, Francis (Box 42)
  - Perry, Henry (Box 42)
  - Persons, Elbert L. (Box 42)
  - Persons, Elizabeth Anderson (Box 42)
  - Peschel, Ernst (Box 42)
  - Peterlin, Anton (Box 42)
  - Peters, Calvin R. (Box 42)
  - Peters, Melvin K. (Box 42)
  - Peterson, Hugh C. (Box 42)
  - Peterson, Myron Boyd (Box 42)
  - Pethia, Robert (Box 42)
  - Petry, Ray (Box 42)
  - Petty, Olan (Box 42)
  - Pfeiffer, Eric (Box 42)
  - Phelps, Leland R. (Box 42)
  - Phelps, Ruth (Box 42)
  - Phelps, Stephen F. (Box 42)
  - Phillips, George, Jr. (Box 42)
  - Phillips, James H. (Box 42)
  - Philpott, Jane (Box 42)
  - Pickrell, Kenneth (Box 43)
  - Pine, Leo (Box 43)
  - Pinkerton, Margaret Isabel (Box 43)
  - Piper, Don C. (Box 43)
  - Piper, Otto A. (Box 43)
  - Pittillo, Robert A. (Box 43)
  - Pitts, William R. (Box 43)
  - Pledger, (Detective) M.A. (Box 43)
  - Pless, John G. (Box 43)
  - Plumb, Bruce (Box 43)
  - Polanyi, Michael (Box 43)
  - Politano, Victor A. (Box 43)
  - Pondy, Louis R. (Box 43)
  - Pope, Hilda (Box 43)
  - Pope, Liston (Box 43)
  - Popkin, Richard H. (Box 43)
  - Porter, Earl W. (Box 43)
  - Porter, F. Ross (Box 43)
  - Porter, F. Stanley (Box 43)
  - Portes, Alejandro (Box 43)
  - Postlethwait, Raymond W. (Box 43)
  - Poston, Mary (Box 43)
  - Poteat, James D. (Box 43)
  - Poteat, Mary (Box 43)
  - Pouagare, Marios C. (Box 43)
  - Powell, Benjamin Edward, (2 Folders) (Box 43)
  - Powell, Rufus H., III (Box 43)
  - Powell, Thomas (Box 43)
  - Prangue, Harry D. (Box 43)
  - Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 43)
  - Pratt, J. Gaither (Box 43)
  - Pratt, Lanier (Box 43)
  - Price, Mary Kathleen (Kathie) (Box 44)
  - Predmore, Richard Lionel (Box 44)
  - Preiss, Jack J. (Box 44)
  - Preston, Richard Arthur (Box 44)
  - Price, James L., Jr. (Box 44)
  - Pride, Cletis (Box 44)
  - Prioletti, Vienna (Box 44)
  - Proctor, Arthur Marcus (Box 44)
  - Proctor, Jesse Harris, Jr. (Box 44)
  - Protter, Phillip E. (Box 44)
  - Proud, Paul P. (Box 44)
  - Pullias, Earl Vivon (Box 44)
  - Pupkin, Marcos J. (Box 44)
  - Pye, Kenneth, (3 Folders) (Box 44)
  - Quaintance, Richard E., Jr. (Box 44)
  - Queen, Vergil (Box 44)
  - Quin, Louis D. (Box 44)
  - Quinn, Galen W. (Box 44)
  - Quynn, Dorothy Mackay (Box 44)
  - Quynn, William Rogers (Box 44)
  - Raben, Milton (Box 44)
  - Radin, Max (Box 44)
  - Rainwater, Roland William (Box 45)
  - Raitt, Jill (Box 45)
  - Rajagopal, R. (Box 45)
  - Ralston, Charles William (Box 45)
  - Ram, (Major) C.H. (Box 45)
  - Ram, Panol Chir (Box 45)
  - Ramsey, Sarah H. (Box 45)
  - Raney, Richard Beverly (Box 45)
  - Rankin, Robert S., (3 Folders) (Box 45)
  - Rankin, William W., Jr. (Box 45)
  - Ranson, Guy Harvey (Box 45)
  - Ranson, Russell (Box 45)
  - Rao, K.R. (Box 45)
  - Raper, Edward S. (Box 45)
  - Rappaport, Josephine (Box 45)
  - Ratchford, Benjamin Ulysses, (2 Folders) (Box 45)
  - Rath, John (Box 45)
  - Rauckman, Elmer J. (Box 45)
  - Ravitz, L.J. (Box 45)
  - Ray, Mel (Box 45)
  - Raymond, Mary Louis (Box 45)
  - Read, Frank Thompson (Box 45)
  - Reagan, Janet M. (Box 45)
  - Reamer, I. Thomas (Box 45)
  - Reardon, Kenneth James (Box 45)
  - Reckless, John (Box 46)
  - Redding, Frances (Box 46)
  - Reed, Frederick Jerome (Box 46)
  - Reeves, Robert James (Box 46)
  - Reichenberg-Hackett, Wally (Box 46)
  - Reid, J.H. Stewart (Box 46)
  - Reid, John T. (Box 46)
  - Reiman, Donald H. (Box 46)
  - Reintgen, Douglas (Box 46)
  - Reiss, Edmund A. (Box 46)
  - Reiter, Mary (Box 46)
  - Renager, Burt W., Jr. (Box 46)
  - Reuben, Lucy (Box 46)
  - Reynolds, Thomas D. (Box 46)
  - Reznick, Bruce A. (Box 46)
  - Rhine, Joseph Banks, (5 Folders) (Box 46)
  - Rhine, Joseph Banks, (9 Folders) (Box 47)
  - Rhine, Joseph Banks, (3 Folders) (Box 48)
  - Rhine, Louise (Box 48)
  - Rhoads, John McFarlane (Box 48)
  - Rice, Douglas (Box 48)
  - Richard, Carole (Box 48)
  - Richards, George J. (Box 48)
  - Ricketts, Mac L. (Box 48)
  - Riddel, Joseph (Box 48)
  - Riedel, Eberhard Karl (Box 48)
  - Rinehart, Robert F. (Box 48)